Guide to the Stanford University, Department of Geology, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Records
  - Student records, 1965-1975
    - Egert, Ernesto (Box 14)
    - Elliott, Terence M. (Box 14)
    - Engelbrekts, Hans Eric (Box 14)
    - Ervine, Warren B. (Box 14)
    - El-Hawat, Ahmed Soleh (Box 14)
    - Ellen, Stephenson D. (Box 14)
    - El Bousti, Ismail Mudathir (Box 14)
    - Elliott, James E. (Box 14)
    - Ester, Donald W. (Box 14)
    - Estrada, H. Armando (Box 14)
    - Everett, Allan T. (Box 14)
    - Eweida, Eweida, Ahmed (Box 14)
    - Ewing, Rodney C. (Box 14)
    - Eyzaguirre, Victor R. (Box 14)
    - Frizzell Jr., Virgil A. (Box 15)
    - Faggioli, Justin M. (Box 15)
    - Fairchild, Thomas R. (Box 15)
    - Fenn, Phillip M. (Box 15)
    - Ferry, John H. (Box 15)
    - Finch, Christian C. (Box 15)
    - Fisher, Weston A. (Box 15)
    - Fleck, Robert J. (Box 15)
    - Fleming, Robert W. (Box 15)
    - Frost, John E. (Box 15)
    - Fuenzalida-P, Richardo Hector (Box 15)
    - Fox, Kenneth Francis (Box 15)
    - Farman, John M. (Box 15)
    - Forbes, Andrew M. (Box 15)
    - Gadong, Antonio (Box 15)
    - Gale, Robert E. (Box 15)
    - Ganahl, John F. (Box 15)
    - George, Ronald A. (Box 15)
    - Gibbs, Allison D. (Box 15)
    - Gilbert, Wyatt G. (Box 15)
    - Giovanella, Carlo A. (Box 15)
    - Glenn, Lawrence E. (Box 15)
    - Gomez, Jose D'Heureux (Box 15)
    - Goodsmi, Jerry L. (Box 15)
    - Grantz, Arthur (Box 15)
    - Greewood, Richard J. (Box 15)
    - Grosenbaugh, Mark A. (Box 15)
    - Gutmann, James T. (Box 15)
    - Hall, Jeffrey S. (Box 15)
    - Hallberg, Jack A. (Box 15)
    - Hamilton, Douglas (Box 15)
    - Hamish, Norman (Box 15)
    - Hampton, Monty A. (Box 15)
    - Hankey, John E. (Box 15)
    - Harden, Deborah R. (Box 15)
    - Harsh, Philip W. (Box 15)
    - Harwood, Robert J. (Box 15)
    - Hay, Peter W. (Box 15)
    - Heffern, Edward L. (Box 15)
    - Heinricho, Christopher N. (Box 15)
    - Hickman, Robert G. (Box 15)
    - Hinderman, Tom K. (Box 15)
    - Hodges, Carol A. (Box 15)
    - Hozer, Thomas L. (Box 15)
    - Holcombe, Rodney J. (Box 15)
    - Hornberger, G. M. (Box 15)
    - Houghton, John C. (Box 15)
    - Howard, James C. (Box 15)
    - Howard, James H. (Box 15)
    - Huerta, Robert D. (Box 15)
    - Hunner, Walter C. (Box 15)
    - Husain, Balgeeguddia (Box 15)
    - Huston, John H. (Box 15)
    - Hylands, James J. (Box 15)
    - Inderbritzen, Anton L. (Box 15)
    - Irish, Peter F. (Box 15)
    - Jackson, Lionel E. (Box 15)
    - James, Lawrence P. (Box 15)
    - James, Odette F. (Box 15)
    - Jenkins, Eleanor (Box 15)
    - Johnson, Robert L. (Box 15)
    - Johnson, Samuel E. (Box 15)
    - Jones, Brian K. (Box 15)
    - Jones, Louis M. (Box 15)
    - Juilland, Jean D. (Box 15)
    - Katchadoorian, Ruebey (Box 16)
    - Koehler, Charles (Box 16)
    - Kaiser, David K. (Box 16)
    - Kelly, Joseph M. (Box 16)
    - Kelly, Kevin (Box 16)
    - Kent, James D. (Box 16)
    - King, Robert W. (Box 16)
    - Kinney, William C. (Box 16)
    - Kirby, Stephen H. (Box 16)
    - Koski, Randolf A. (Box 16)
    - Kuntz, Mel Anton (Box 16)
    - Kurfess, William R. (Box 16)
    - Lamon, Kathryn A. (Box 16)
    - Lawrence, Robert D. (Box 16)
    - Lee, Keenan (Box 16)
    - Le Masurier, Wesley E. (Box 16)
    - Ligget, William (Box 16)
    - Lima, David J. (Box 16)
    - Lindguist, Mary Lou (Box 16)
    - Loayza, Oscar H. (Box 16)
    - Lobo-Querrero, A. (Box 16)
    - Long, Philip E. (Box 16)
    - Londero, Murphy J. L. (Box 16)
    - Lorenz, Christoph W. (Box 16)
    - Longhridger, Mark (Box 16)
    - Luce, Robert W. (Box 16)
    - Fudington, Stephen D. (Box 16)
    - Lefkin, John L. (Box 16)
    - Lujan, Miquel A. (Box 16)
    - McCloud, Kimball (Box 16)
    - McCracken, Willard A. (Box 16)
    - McEwen, James A. (Box 16)
    - McHendrie, (Andrew) G. (Box 16)
    - McGee, Steward (Box 16)
    - McLean, Dewey (Box 16)
    - McLeroy, Donald F. (Box 16)
    - McNellis, Jesse M. (Box 16)
    - Machado Brito, Ignacio Aureliano (Box 16)
    - Mack Seymour (Box 16)
    - Makhloref, Ahmed (Box 16)
    - Malfait, Bruce (Box 16)
    - Malin, Peter E. (Box 16)
    - Manda, Michael L. (Box 16)
    - Mannian, Lawrence (Box 16)
    - Mansfield, Charles F. (Box 16)
    - Mark, Robert K. (Box 16)
    - Marshall, Claude Monte Jr. (Box 16)
    - Martin, Conrad (Box 16)
    - Martin, Robert F. (Box 16)
    - Martinez, Maximo V. (Box 16)
    - Martinez, T. Louis Eduardo (Box 16)
    - Matsushige, Gary S. (Box 16)
    - Miller, Fred K. (Box 16)
    - Miller, Thomas P. (Box 16)
    - Mills, Joy Ellen T. (Box 16)
    - Mills, Richard A. (Box 16)
    - Missallati, Amid Abdulla (Box 16)
    - Moiseeff, Alexis N. (Box 16)
    - Molz, Fred (Box 16)
    - Montgomery, Philip O. (Box 16)
    - Moore, John H. (Box 16)
    - Moore, Richard T. (Box 16)
    - Morrow, William B. (Box 16)
    - Muraro, Theodore W. (Box 16)
    - Mustart, David A. (Box 16)
    - Naseef, Abdullah O. (Box 17)
    - Neff, Thomas R. (Box 17)
    - Nelson, Robert E. (Box 17)
    - Nelson, Peter A. (Box 17)
    - Nichols, Kathy (Box 17)
    - Nicolet, Bernard (Box 17)
    - Normark, William R. (Box 17)
    - Ojakangas, Dennis R. (Box 17)
    - Ordonez, George E. (Box 17)
    - Orr, James MacPhail (Box 17)
    - Ortiz, Francisco (Box 17)
    - Querol, Suni F. (Box 17)
    - Radtke, Arthur (Box 17)
    - Raymond, Alonzo A. (Box 17)
    - Reedy, David J. (Box 17)
    - Reeves, R. (Box 17)
    - Rennick, Walter L. (Box 17)
    - Richmond, William o. (Box 17)
    - Ribeiro, Mauricio (Box 17)
    - Rich, Ernest I. (Box 17)
    - Robinson, Allen C. (Box 17)
    - Rosenbaum, James G. (Box 17)
    - Rubio, (Reyes) Rafael A. (Box 17)
    - Ruble, Robert T. (Box 17)
    - Radfield, Earl P. (Box 17)
    - Paces, Tomas (Box 17)
    - Pastor, Sergio (Box 17)
    - Payne, William D. (Box 17)
    - Pentsil, Benjamin K. (Box 17)
    - Pering, Katherine L. (Box 17)
    - Pestrong, Raymond (Box 17)
    - Peterson, Frank L. (Box 17)
    - Peterson, Fred (Box 17)
    - Phillips, Douglas A. (Box 17)
    - Piaggio, Arthur D. (Box 17)
    - Pike, Jane E. Neilson (Box 17)
    - Psiciotto, Kenneth A. (Box 17)
    - Plafker, George (Box 17)
    - Plagge, Warner E. (Box 17)
    - Platt, Jeremy B. (Box 17)
    - Player, Gary (Box 17)
    - Polkowski, George R. (Box 17)
    - Pollard, David D. (Box 17)
    - Prelat, Alfredo E. (Box 17)
    - Price, Charles E. Jr. (Box 17)
    - Peeffer, John H. (Box 17)
    - Pugh, David A. (Box 17)
    - Sainsburg, Cleo L. (Box 17)
    - Salas, Guillermo A. (Box 17)
    - Salem, Bruce B. (Box 17)
    - Saxon, Harris (Box 17)
    - Savy, Jean (Box 17)
    - Searpell, Wilson (Box 17)
    - Schirra, Walter M. (Box 17)
    - Schneider, Steven B. (Box 17)
    - Schoettler, John H. (Box 17)
    - Sbeta, Ali M. (Box 17)
    - Schweickert, Richard A. (Box 17)
    - Sears, Carol (Box 17)
    - Seck, Hans A. (Box 17)
    - Seyfert, Carl (Box 18)
    - Sellect, William L. (Box 18)
    - Sedore, Jaquelin J. (Box 18)
    - Sheridan, Michael F. (Box 18)
    - Shen, Henry Yi-Ming (Box 18)
    - Shih, John S. F. (Box 18)
    - Sides, James W. (Box 18)
    - Silitongo, Paruhum (Box 18)
    - Simonds, Charles H. (Box 18)
    - Sitan, Nicholas (Box 18)
    - Smith, James G. (Box 18)
    - Smith, Mark J. (Box 18)
    - Smith, Roger S. (Box 18)
    - Snetsinger, Kenneth G. (Box 18)
    - Snoke, Arthur W. (Box 18)
    - Snyder, Walter S. (Box 18)
    - Soule, Courtney E. (Box 18)
    - Sowards, Steven (Box 18)
    - Spencer, James W. (Box 18)
    - Spieker, Andrew (Box 18)
    - Squire, Horace C. (Box 18)
    - Squyres, John B. (Box 18)
    - Sramek, Bruce (Box 18)
    - Stauffer, Peter H. (Box 18)
    - Steiner, Jeffrey C. (Box 18)
    - Stephens, Daniel B. (Box 18)
    - Steward, Richard J. (Box 18)
    - Strausz, David A. (Box 18)
    - Stuart, Alexander D. (Box 18)
    - Stuckless, John S. (Box 18)
    - Susman, Kenneth Roger (Box 18)
    - Swanson, Samuel E. (Box 18)
    - Swe, Win (Box 18)
    - Taber, JaJ es (Box 18)
    - Taylor, Charles M. (Box 18)
    - Taylor, Werner F. (Box 18)
    - Thigpen, John B. (Box 18)
    - Tello, C. M. (Box 18)
    - Thompson, Laird B. (Box 18)
    - Tibana, Paublo (Box 18)
    - Tieh, Thomas (Box 18)
    - Tipton, Ann (Box 18)
    - Todd, Victoria R. (Box 18)
    - Turk, Leland J. (Box 18)
    - (Ruderman) Turner, Barbara L. (Box 18)
    - Tuthill, Rosalind L. (Box 18)
    - Tyson, Robert R. (Box 18)
    - Veatch, Maurice D. (Box 18)
    - Vennum, Walter R. (Box 18)
    - Vonder, Linden K. (Box 18)
    - Wagstaff, Donald A. (Box 18)
    - Walklet, Donn C. (Box 18)
    - Waltz, James (Box 18)
    - Warner, Richard D. (Box 18)
    - Warren, John S. (Box 18)
    - Wei, Chang Hsin (Box 18)
    - Wiebe, Robert A. (Box 18)
    - Whitney, James A. (Box 18)
    - White, James R. (Box 18)
    - Williams, Stephen L. (Box 18)
    - Winkler, Gary R. (Box 18)
    - Wobus, Reinhard A. (Box 18)
    - Wodzicki, Antoni (Box 18)
    - Wong, Steven J. (Box 18)
    - Woods, Jay A. (Box 18)
    - Wright, Raymont A. (Box 18)
    - Yock, Dianne (Box 18)
    - Zantop, Half A. (Box 18)
    - Zelinger, Sheile L. (Box 18)
    - Zucker, Melvin B. (Box 18)
  - Student records, 1975-1977
    - Barnard, Juliana H (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Baker, James B (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Baker, Peter (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Bassett, Randy Lynn (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Bauder, Janet May (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Blank, Jennifer Glee (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Block, Nicholas C (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Bookstrom, Arthur A. (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Bose, Sudip Kumar (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Christensen, Odin (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Connor, Cathy Lynn (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Dalrymple, Nark (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Damassa, Sarah T. (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Dellinger, David A (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Dubray, Edward A (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Dupre, William R. (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Fink, Kendrick C. (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Fitch, Frank W. III (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Foard, Eugene E. (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Garcia, Brenda J (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Gaul, Peter J (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Gillam, Mary L (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Gilman, Jeffrey A. (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Gilmore, Thomas D (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Halbo, Ka ren E. (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Harding, Lucy E. (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Hartley, Paul D. (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Hickman, Carole J (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Hill, Carolyn E (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Hodge, Elizabeth T. (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Hodson, Gregory F. (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Honea, Elmont G. (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Howard, Daggett H. Jr. (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Howe, Stephen J (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Howland, Mark D (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Huffington, Terry L. (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - Ingersoll, Raymond V. II (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Jackson, Nancy C (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - Jansma, Pamela E (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - Jenke, James A (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - Jenke, John H. (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - Keller, Chester K. (Box 19, Folder 42)
    - Koski, Randolph (Box 19, Folder 43)
    - Kososki, Bruce A. (Box 19, Folder 44)
    - Lambert, Richard J. (Box 19, Folder 45)
    - Lewis, Anita Fay (Box 19, Folder 46)
    - Lindberg, Charles A. (Box 19, Folder 47)
    - McHendric, Andrew G (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - McMasters, Catherine R (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Maehr, Ted H. (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Maggard, Jacque (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Marval, Francisco R. (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Mango, Patrice D. (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - May, Rodd James (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Minobe, Wayne A., Removed 1986 Sep 22 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Me tca lf, Ricahrd C. (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Modrall, James R. (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Neill, William M. (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Nelson, Roger M. (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Newman, Mark C. (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Nicholson, Thomas J. (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Nordstog, Kim T. (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Nutt, Constance J. (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Nyambok, Isaac (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Oberste-Lehn, Deane (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Parker, Harry M. (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Peterson, Bradford A. (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Peterson, Jocelyn A. (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Poland, Joseph F. (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Reches, Ze'ev (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Reeder, John W. (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Rindsberg, Andrew K. (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Rodine, James D. (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Ruddock, Stephen F. (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Ruetz, Joseph W. (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Salvador, Phillip (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Scofield, David H. (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Segall, Paul (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Simon, Margie Sue (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Sitar, Nicholas (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - Smith, Gregory M. (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - Steltenpohl, Greg A. (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - Suter, Sherman J. (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - Taylor, Bruce E. (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - Telleen, Kenneth Ed. (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - Thrupp, Gordon A. (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - Tinsley, John C. III (Box 20, Folder 40)
    - Tormey, Daniel R. (Box 20, Folder 41)
    - Trautmann, Charles H. (Box 20, Folder 42)
    - Tripathi, Vijay S. (Box 20, Folder 43)
    - Walker, Michael P. (Box 20, Folder 44)
    - Wiggins, Brian D. (Box 20, Folder 45)
    - Wilbur, Curtis L. (Box 20, Folder 46)
    - Wright, Raymond M. (Box 20, Folder 47)
- Student files, 1977-1985; Accession ARCH-1993-094
  - A - By (Box 1)
  - Ca - Ec (Box 2)
  - Es - He (Box 3)
  - Hi - K (Box 4)
  - La - N (Box 5)
  - Ob - Shi (Box 6)
  - Si - Tu (Box 7)
  - V - Wh (Box 8)
  - Wi - Z (Box 9)